domains.lk 2017-06-18

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes the commitment of LK Domain Registry (LK Domain) to the privacy of information collected from its customers. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to provide Users with an understanding of what types of information we collect, how we treat it, and choices they may have related to this information. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time.

**Collection of Personal Data  
**  
The LK Domain Registry collects your personal data for the following purposes:

i. Administering registration of .lk domain names;  
ii. Maintenance and/or operation of the .lk domain name registry;  
iii. Receiving and dealing with customers’ enquiries and/or complaints by third parties;  
iv. Obtaining your feedback on our services; and  
v. General record keeping in the course of LK Domain Registry’s operations.

Unless stated otherwise, the personal data required is obligatory to be provided by you. Should you fail to provide such obligatory personal data, LK Domain will be unable to process your request for services and/or assist you in providing the service(s) requested by you.

LK Domain may also use your personal data to inform you of updates from LK Domain, which may include price promotions, new services or products, customer satisfaction surveys, etc.

LK Domain collects personal data directly from you and/or from the agents registered with LK Domain.

**Security and Retention of Personal Data  
**  
LK Domain implements security measures to protect your personal data against unauthorized access, misuse, disclosure, copying, use, alteration, accidental loss or theft, destruction or damage. Such security measures include technical protection of LK Domain’s system, and training of LK Domain staff.  
The Security Policy is aimed to protect the confidentiality, integrity and availability of LK Domain’s critical information, processing facilities and services that include your personal data.

**Disclosure of Personal Data  
**  
LK Domain may disclose your personal data to our duly appointed partners that assist LK Domain to provide you with LK Domain services such as:

• .lk domain registration services  
• .lk domain customer care and related activities  
• .lk domain charging and billing purposes  
• .lk domain technical support purposes  
• .lk domain marketing and its related activities (including market research) and/or  
• any other .lk domain services necessary for the general care and management of your registration with LK Domain.

LK Domain will ensure that the appointed agents shall only use and process your personal data for the purpose(s) it was collected for by LK Domain, and adopt appropriate technical and organizational security measures when processing your personal data.

In addition to the above purposes and for such other purposes as may be required by law, LK Domain will not disclose, sell, trade or rent your personal information to any other third party unless your prior consent has been obtained.

**Right of Review  
**  
LK Domain reserves the right to review and amend this Policy from time to time.
